<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Yahoo! Finance: PHG News</title><copyright>Copyright (c) 2016 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright><link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=phg</link><description>Latest Financial News for Koninklijke Philips N.V. NY Reg</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 13:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/brand/purplelogo/uh/us/fin.gif</url><title>Yahoo! Finance: PHG News</title><link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=phg</link><width>144</width><height>45</height></image><item><title>Do these Household Names Still Woo Investors - AAPL, PHG, SNE, and HAR</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/household-names-still-woo-investors-130000990.html</link><description>[Accesswire] - NEW YORK, NY / ACCESSWIRE / April 19, 2016 / Living in an age of technological revolution, our lives practically revolve around myriads of electronic devices - from smartphones to computers. So when one ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/4292028256</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elekta and Philips Begin Installation of MR-Guided Linear Accelerator at The Netherlands Cancer Institute</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/elekta-philips-begin-installation-mr-053000389.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - Elekta (EKTA-B.ST), Royal Philips (NYSE:PHG, AEX:PHIA) and The Netherlands Cancer Institute, (NKI, Amsterdam, The Netherlands) today announced the installation of a high-field (1.5 Tesla) MR-guided linear accelerator (MR-linac) system. The Elekta MR-linac is designed to capture high-quality images of tumors and surrounding tissue, allowing physicians to rapidly assess and respond by modifying the radiation treatment, a responsive intervention approach. The Netherlands Cancer Institute is a member of the Elekta MR-linac Consortium, founded in 2012 by Elekta and technology partner Royal Philips.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/4259343212</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips Lighting welcomes iGuzzini as licensee to EnabLED Licensing Program</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=128l10ekh/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/BF35B5803D37B35A704A5B90C6112F95128C5046</link><description>[at noodls] - Amsterdam, The Netherlands - Philips Lighting, the global leader in lighting and a wholly owned subsidiary of Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG, AEX: PHI), today announced that it entered into a patent license ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/4036868146</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 07:42:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips notifies the Netherlands Authority for the Financial Markets of a 3.02% interest in its issued share capital</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=128jchltp/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/EA7BA260870124A41E4158912BF2D070B3FBE477</link><description>[at noodls] - Amsterdam, the Netherlands - Royal Philips (NYSE:PHG, AEX:PHIA) announced today that it has notified the Netherlands Authority for the Financial Markets (AFM) that it currently holds a 3.02 percent interest ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2057928413</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 07:17:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Melrose Reportedly Abandons Bid for Philips Lighting Unit</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/melrose-reportedly-abandons-bid-philips-191007549.html</link><description></description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/3881395094</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 19:10:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips Said to Name Banks For Possible Lighting Unit IPO</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/bloomberg/rss/SIG=13d3rb4de/*http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-04-04/philips-said-to-name-banks-for-possible-lighting-unit-ipo?cmpid=yhoo.headline</link><description></description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/345893611</guid><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 14:19:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Melrose Said to Drop Out of Race for Philips Lighting Unit</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/bloomberg/rss/SIG=13h9m5e9q/*http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-04-03/melrose-said-to-drop-out-of-bidding-for-philips-lighting-unit?cmpid=yhoo.headline</link><description></description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/3016260654</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 19:19:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Melrose Said to Drop Out of Bidding for Philips Lighting Unit</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/melrose-said-drop-bidding-philips-191925591.html</link><description></description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/106784174</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 19:19:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips showcases innovative cardiology solutions at 2016 American College of Cardiology Conference</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/philips-showcases-innovative-cardiology-solutions-144200663.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - AMSTERDAM, April 1, 2016 /PRNewswire/ -- Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG; AEX: PHIA) today announced its participation in the 2016 American College of Cardiology&apos;s Annual Scientific Session and Expo (ACC.16), ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/1820079428</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 14:42:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips introduces first commercial MR-only solution for prostate cancer treatment planning in the U.S.</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=128esousf/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/3BCC426DA661ECBB01C487464659498073FBAA20</link><description>[at noodls] - Amsterdam, The Netherlands - Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG; AEX: PHIA) today introduced the first commercially available MR-only simulation solution indicated for prostate cancer radiation oncology treatment ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2962592220</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 06:46:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple Drops Osram, Adds Philips LEDs to Top Suppliers List</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/bloomberg/rss/SIG=13gvpmhjl/*http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-03-31/apple-drops-osram-adds-philips-leds-to-top-200-supplier-list?cmpid=yhoo.headline</link><description></description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2227758467</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 17:46:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips’ design excellence recognized with 37 prestigious Red Dot awards in 2016</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=12861bkit/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/707114014CFF62908C0DDD278DFBB892353BC5DE</link><description>[at noodls] - Amsterdam, the Netherlands - Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG, AEX: PHI) today announced that it has received 37 awards at the 2016 &apos;Red Dot Award: Product Design &apos;. With 5,214 products from 57 countries submitted ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/3896544703</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 08:40:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips and Vodafone join forces for connected lighting and smart city services</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=1286udupr/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/89E6B25142A3444E962036FE2C9D4410770108AB</link><description>[at noodls] - Frankfurt, Germany - Philips Lighting, a Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG, AEX: PHIA) company and the global leader in lighting, announced today a new agreement for Vodafone to become a global Internet of Things ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/975284615</guid><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 08:30:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Enjoy good days and good nights with Philips Hue white ambiance</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=128mslgna/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/89AB9A708A9B492515D7FE291425BE1A1D55B611</link><description>[at noodls] - Frankfurt, Germany - Philips Lighting, a Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG, AEX: PHIA) company and global leader in lighting, unlocks the power of white light with Philips Hue white ambiance. Inspired by the sun, ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/1915876436</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 14:56:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Study Finds Philips LED Lights Provide Improved Energy Efficiency and Production for Growing Food Crops in Space</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=1280g8v85/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/99251CC5A396EC7275FB58F34E0359819F96BD3F</link><description>[at noodls] - University of Arizona and Philips Lighting collaborated to create improved lighting for plant production in Mars-lunar greenhouses Non-water cooled LED lights used 56% less energy; more than doubling production ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/152878539</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 14:56:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips Lighting takes light beyond illumination</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=128j9vcba/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/497C2A5029A41BA5E226DF1C7ED75BA83F88CAF4</link><description>[at noodls] - Extends lighting leadership into the Internet of Things (IoT) unlocking new experiences and value for customers Announces connected innovations, customers and partnerships for street lighting, retail, ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2201361056</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 14:56:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips introduces first commercial MR-only solution for prostate cancer treatment planning in the U.S.</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/philips-introduces-first-commercial-mr-130000614.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - AMSTERDAM, March 30, 2016 /PRNewswire/ -- Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG; AEX: PHIA) today introduced the first commercially available MR-only simulation solution indicated for prostate cancer radiation oncology ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/1529631616</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Philips convenes the 2016 Annual General Meeting of Shareholders</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=128v227c4/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/BF818DDD9E77075FF23701396C1B33F9047C5A2D</link><description>[at noodls] - Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG, AEX: PHIA) is a leading health technology company focused on improving people&apos;s health and enabling better outcomes across the health continuum from healthy living and prevention, ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2375190305</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 07:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts General Hospital embarks on clinical analytical study using Philips&apos; IntelliSite Solution to advance digital pathology adoption in the United States</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/massachusetts-general-hospital-embarks-clinical-130000907.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - AMSTERDAM, March 29, 2016 /PRNewswire/ -- Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG, AEX: PHIA) today announced Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH) will serve as a key testing site for a multi-centered instrument precision study involving Philips&apos; digital pathology whole slide imaging (WSI) IntelliSite Solution. The study is designed to show the reproducibility of the IntelliSite pathology solution in disease detection as part of the industry&apos;s efforts to obtain regulatory clearance of WSI for primary diagnostic use. If approved for diagnosis, in contrast to the industry&apos;s current analog process, soon pathologists could benefit from a digital system for their routine work.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/1546964297</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Massachusetts General Hospital embarks on clinical analytical study using Philips’ IntelliSite Solution to advance digital pathology adoption in the United States</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/noodlsaunz/rss/SIG=128s2iv7f/*http://www.publicnow.com/view/445FCB85A045A7C07140D5B1E6ED88FA62FB837C</link><description>[at noodls] - Amsterdam, The Netherlands - Royal Philips (NYSE: PHG, AEX: PHIA) today announced Massachusetts General Hospital (MGH) will serve as a key testing site for a multi-centered instrument precision study involving ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/1501638437</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 12:07:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>